Inventory of the G. Walter Mapp Papers 1895-1935
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- Correspondence of G. Walter Mapp, 1895-1935. (Box 1-8)
  - Correspondence Relating to the 1918 Congressional Democratic Primary, 1918. (Box 7-8)
    - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 147 items. (Box-folder 8:23-29)
      - Correspondence with residents of Mathews County: Wi, 1918., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:29)
    - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 211 items. (Box-folder 8:30-34)
      - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County: A-C, 1918., 22 items. (Box-folder 8:30)
      - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County: D-F, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:31)
      - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County: G-L, 1918., 23 items. (Box-folder 8:32)
      - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County: M-P, 1918., 22 items. (Box-folder 8:33)
      - Correspondence with residents of Middlesex County: R-W, 1918., 34 items. (Box-folder 8:34)
    - Correspondence with residents of Newport News, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 69 items. (Box-folder 8:35-37)
      - Correspondence with residents of Newport News: B-D, 1918., 24 items. (Box-folder 8:35)
      - Correspondence with residents of Newport News: E-M, 1918., 32 items. (Box-folder 8:36)
      - Correspondence with residents of Newport News: N-W, 1918., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:37)
    - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 172 items. (Box-folder 8:38-45)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: A-C, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:38)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: D-E, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:39)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: F, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:40)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: G-L, 1918., 23 items. (Box-folder 8:41)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: M, 1918., 27 items. (Box-folder 8:42)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: N, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:43)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: S-T, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:44)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northampton County: W, 1918., 25 items. (Box-folder 8:45)
    - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 94 items. (Box-folder 8:46-50)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County: A-B, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:46)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County: C-I, 1918., 22 items. (Box-folder 8:47)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County: J-O, 1918., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:48)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County: P-R, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:49)
      - Correspondence with residents of Northumberland County: S-W, 1918., 15 items. (Box-folder 8:50)
    - Correspondence with residents of Richmond County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:51)
    - Correspondence with residents of Spotsylvania County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 25 items. (Box-folder 8:52)
    - Correspondence with residents of Warwick County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 4 items. (Box-folder 8:53)
    - Correspondence with residents of Westmoreland County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 58 items. (Box-folder 8:54-56)
      - Correspondence with residents of Westmoreland County: A-B, 1918., 25 items. (Box-folder 8:54)
      - Correspondence with residents of Westmoreland County: D-M, 1918., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:55)
      - Correspondence with residents of Westmoreland County: T-W, 1918., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:56)
    - Correspondence with residents of York County, pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 60 items. (Box-folder 8:57-59)
      - Correspondence with residents of York County: A-I, 1918., 24 items. (Box-folder 8:57)
      - Correspondence with residents of York County: L-R, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:58)
      - Correspondence with residents of York County: S-W, 1918., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:59)
    - Correspondence with voters concerning Senator J. O'Connor Goolrick, and pertaining to the 1918, 1st District Congressional Democratic primary, 1918., 24 items. (Box-folder 8:60)
  - Correspondence and receipts pertaining to philanthropic contributions by Mapp, 1919-1932., 44 items. (Box-folder 8:61)
  Series 2: Correspondence of Herbert Barnes
- Correspondence of Herbert Barnes, G. Walter Mapp's law partner, 1923-1933. (Box 8:62-117)
  - Barnes Correspondence: A, 1923-1933., 27 items. (Box-folder 8:62)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Bag-Barc, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:63)
  - Barnes Correspondence: C. B. Barnes, 1930-1933., 14 items. (Box-folder 8:64)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Barnes, E. W., Forrest, and O. T., 1928-1933., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:65)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Webster T. Barnes, 1927-1933., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:66)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Be-Bi, 1923-1933., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:67)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Bl, 1923-1933., 16 items. (Box-folder 8:68)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Bo-Br, 1923-1933., 14 items. (Box-folder 8:69)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Bu-By, 1923-1933., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:70)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ca-Cl, 1923-1933., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:71)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Co, 1925-1931., 14 items. (Box-folder 8:72)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Cr, 1923-1933., 16 items. (Box-folder 8:73)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Cu, 1923-1933., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:74)
  - Barnes Correspondence: D-De, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:75)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Di, 1923-1933., 15 items. (Box-folder 8:76)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Do, 1923-1932., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:77)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Dr-Du, 1923-1933., 14 items. (Box-folder 8:78)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ea-El, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:79)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Em-Ew, 1923-1933., 17 items. (Box-folder 8:80)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Fa-Fl, 1923-1933., 19 items. (Box-folder 8:81)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Fo-Fr, 1923-1933., 10 items. (Box-folder 8:82)
  - Barnes Correspondence: G, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:83)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ha-He, 1923-1933., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:84)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Hi-Hu, 1923-1933., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:85)
  - Barnes Correspondence: I-Jeffries, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:86)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Daniel Jeffries, Chincoteague, Virginia, 1927-1933., 39 items. (Box-folder 8:87)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Jel-Jon, 1923-1933., 11 items. (Box-folder 8:88)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Joy-Ju, 1923., 27 items. (Box-folder 8:89)
  - Barnes Correspondence: K, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:90)
  - Barnes Correspondence: La-Le, 1923-1933., 22 items. (Box-folder 8:91)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Li-Ly, 1923-1933., 16 items. (Box-folder 8:92)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mac-Mapp, George H., 1923-1933., 5 items. (Box-folder 8:93)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mapp, J. Brooks, Margaret, and Virginia, 1925-1933., 29 items. (Box-folder 8:94)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mar-Mas, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:95)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mat, 1923-1933., 17 items. (Box-folder 8:96)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mc-Me, 1923-1933., 16 items. (Box-folder 8:97)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Mi-Mo, 1923-1933., 15 items. (Box-folder 8:98)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ne-Ni, 1923-1933., 8 items. (Box-folder 8:99)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Nock, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:100)
  - Barnes Correspondence: No-Ny, 1923-1933., 9items. (Box-folder 8:101)
  - Barnes Correspondence: O, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:102)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Pa, 1923-1933., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:103)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Pe-Pl, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:104)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Po-Pu, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:105)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ra, 1923-1933., 12 items. (Box-folder 8:106)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ri, 1923-1933., 15 items. (Box-folder 8:107)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Ro-Ru, 1923-1933., 12 items. (Box-folder 8:108)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Sa-Sh, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:109)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Sl-So, 1923-1933., 18 items. (Box-folder 8:110)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Sp-Su, 1923-1933., 13 items. (Box-folder 8:111)
  - Barnes Correspondence: T, 1923-1933., 21 items. (Box-folder 8:112)
  - Barnes Correspondence: U-V, 1923-1933., 7 items. (Box-folder 8:113)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Wa, 1923-1933., 20 items. (Box-folder 8:114)
  - Barnes Correspondence: We, 1923-1933., 9 items. (Box-folder 8:115)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Wh, 1923-1933., 12 items. (Box-folder 8:116)
  - Barnes Correspondence: Wi-Wo, 1923-1933., 17 items. (Box-folder 8:117)
  - Assorted stamps of interest, cancelled and uncancelled, 1900-1934., 12 items. (Box-folder 8:118)
  Series 3: Political Papers
- Political Papers of G. Walter Mapp, 1910-1940. (Box-folder 9:1-70)
  - Newspapers, 1911-1933, n.d. (Box-folder 9:1-26)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1911 state Senate election, 1911., 9 items. (Box-folder 9:1)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1912., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:2)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1914 statewide Prohibition referendum, 1914., 13 items. (Box-folder 9:3)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1914 statewide Prohibition referendum, [1914]., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:4)
    - Newspaper clippings, [1917]., 2 items. (Box-folder 9:5)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1918 Democratic congressional primary, April 1918., 9 items. (Box-folder 9:6)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1918 Democratic primary, May 1918., 11 items. (Box-folder 9:7)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1918 Democratic primary, June-July 1918., 10 items. (Box-folder 9:8)
    - Newspaper clippings, mostly pertaining to the 1918 Democratic primary, August-October 1918., 7 items. (Box-folder 9:9)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1918 Democratic primary, [1918]., 52 items. (Box-folder 9:10)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1920., 8 items. (Box-folder 9:11)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1921., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:12)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1922., 18 items. (Box-folder 9:13)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1925 gubernatorial race, January-April 1923., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:14)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1925 gubernatorial race, May-December 1923., 15 items. (Box-folder 9:15)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1925 gubernatorial race, [1923]., 8 items. (Box-folder 9:16)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1924 Davis-Coolidge presidential campaign, 1924., 7 items. (Box-folder 9:17)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1925 gubernatorial election, 1925., 6 items. (Box-folder 9:18)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1926., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:19)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1927., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:20)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1928 Hoover-Smith presidential campaign, 1928., 16 items. (Box-folder 9:21)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1929 gubernatorial race, February-October 1929., 19 items. (Box-folder 9:22)
    - Newspaper clippings pertaining to the 1929 gubernatorial race, [1929]., 7 items. (Box-folder 9:23)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1930., 2 items. (Box-folder 9:24)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1933., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:25)
    - Newspaper clippings, n.d., 43 items. (Box-folder 9:26)
  - Pamphlets, Speeches and Other Documents, 1910-1940. (Box-folder 9:27-45)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to Prohibition, 1914., 38 items. (Box-folder 9:27)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to Prohibition, ca. 1914., 46 items. (Box-folder 9:28)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to Prohibition, ca. 1914., 10 items. (Box-folder 9:29)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to Prohibition, ca. 1914., 6 items. (Box-folder 9:30)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to Prohibition, ca. 1914., 5 items. (Box-folder 9:31)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to women's suffrage amendment, 1910s., 26 items. (Box-folder 9:32)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the Ku Klux Klan, ca. 1915., 7 items. (Box-folder 9:33)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to motion picture censorship, ca. 1920., 10 items. (Box-folder 9:34)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the War Memorial commission, ca. 1921., 11 items. (Box-folder 9:35)
    - Pamphlets and other documents pertaining to capital punishment, ca. 1920., 12 items. (Box-folder 9:36A)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the Democratic Party of Virginia, ca. 1920s., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:36B)
    - Documents pertaining to the Yorktown Sesquicentennial Commission, 1931., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:36C)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the 1911 state senatorial election, 1911., 8 items. (Box-folder 9:37A)
    - Pamphlets and other miscellaneous documents pertaining to the 1918 Congressional campaign, 1918., 23 items. (Box-folder 9:37B)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the 1922 Virginia senatorial campaign, 1922., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:37C)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the 1924 presidential campaign, 1924., 25 items. (Box-folder 9:38A)
    - Statements pertaining to the 1925 Virginia gubernatorial election, 1925., 2 items. (Box-folder 9:38B)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the 1928 presidential campaign: Pro-Smith, 1928., 20 items. (Box-folder 9:39)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to the 1928 presidential campaign: Anti-Smith, 1928., 12 items. (Box-folder 9:40)
    - Pamphlets and papers pertaining to the 1929 Virginia gubernatorial election, 1929., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:41)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to assorted campaigns, ca. 1920s., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:42)
    - Drafts of speeches by G. Walter Mapp, 1910s-1920s., 30 items. (Box-folder 9:43A)
    - Published speeches by various politicians, 1911-1933., 7 items. (Box-folder 9:43B)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to miscellaneous politicians topics, 1910s-1920., 10 items. (Box-folder 9:44A)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to World War II and to Roosevelt's re-election campaign, 1940., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:44B)
    - Pamphlets pertaining to miscellaneous non-political topics, 1910s-1920s., 12 items. (Box-folder 9:45)
  - Bills, Resolutions and Amendments, 1910-1920. (Box-folder 9:46-54)
    - Published senate bills, ca. 1910s-1920s., 9 items. (Box-folder 9:46)
    - Published house bills and joint resolutions, ca. 1910s-1920s., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:47)
    - Typewritten drafts of senate bills, ca. 1910s-1920s., 17 items. (Box-folder 9:48)
    - Typewritten drafts of senate bills, ca. 1910s-1920s., 5 items. (Box-folder 9:49)
    - Typewritten drafts of joint resolutions, 1910s-1920s., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:50)
    - Typewritten drafts of senate amendments, 1910s-1920s., 18 items. (Box-folder 9:51)
    - Handwritten notes and bills by Mapp pertaining to his work in the Virginia Senate, 1910s-1920s., 15 items. (Box-folder 9:52)
    - Voting list and records of the Virginia House of Delegates, Senate and Joint Democratic Caucus, 1912-1920., 32 items. (Box-folder 9:53)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets and typewritten papers pertaining to Mapp's work in the Virginia Senate, 1910s-1920s., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:54)
  - Voters/Voting Lists and Tallies, 1910-1920. (Box-folder 9:55-70)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets and typewritten papers pertaining to Mapp's work in the Virginia Senate, 1910s-1920s., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:55)
    - List of voters in Accomac County, 1911., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:56)
    - List of voters in Accomac County, May 1913., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:57)
    - List of voters in Accomac County, December 1913., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:58)
    - List of voters in Accomac County, 1915., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:59)
    - List of voters in Accomac County, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:60)
    - Lists of voters in Matthews County, 1913-1916., 4 items. (Box-folder 9:61)
    - Lists of voters in Northumberland County, 1914-1918., 3 items. (Box-folder 9:62)
    - Lists of voters in Spotsylvania County, 1913., 2 items. (Box-folder 9:63)
    - List of voters in Warwick County, 1918., 1 item. (Box-folder 9:64)
    - Precinct rolls of voters on the Eastern Shore, 1910s-1920s., 42 items. (Box-folder 9:65)
    - Hand and typewritten lists of Mapp supporters in Virginia's 1st District, 1910s-1920s., 71 items. (Box-folder 9:66)
    - Handwritten voting tallies, 1910s-1920s., 14 items. (Box-folder 9:67)
    - Typewritten voting tallies, 1910s-1920s., 24 items. (Box-folder 9:68)
    - Petitions for various issues, 1914-1932., 29 items. (Box-folder 9:69)
    - Resolutions of various topics, 1914-1933., 30 items. (Box-folder 9:70)
  Series 4: Legal and/or Business Papers
- Legal Papers and/or Business Papers, 1895-1935, n.d. (Box 9-10)
  - Legal Cases, 1905-1931. (Box-folder 9:71-73)
    - Letters and documents pertaining to the Burroughs Case, 1905-1907., 25 items. (Box-folder 9:71)
    - Letters and documents pertaining to the Mace Case, 1910., 35 items. (Box-folder 9:72)
    - Documents pertaining to the Matthews Case, 1931., 5 items. (Box-folder 9:73)
  - Material Pertaining to Various Estates, 1908-1912. (Box 9-10)
    - Documents pertaining to the estate of George W. Covington, 1911., 17 items. (Box-folder 9:74)
    - Documents pertaining to the estate of William T. Mason, 1911-1912., 11 items. (Box-folder 10:1)
    - Demands on the estate of William T. Mason, 1911-1912., 15 items. (Box-folder 10:2)
    - Checks and receipts of the estate of William T. Mason, 1911-1912., 23 items. (Box-folder 10:3)
    - Documents pertaining to the estate of Sylvester Purnell, 1908-1910., 4 items. (Box-folder 10:4)
    - Demands on the estate of Sylvester Purnell, 1908-1910., 54 items. (Box-folder 10:5)
    - Checks on the estate of Sylvester Purnell, 1908-1909., 20 items. (Box-folder 10:6)
  - Miscellaneous legal documents, 1900-1930., 22 items. (Box-folder 10:7)
  - Handwritten notes pertaining to assorted legal cases, 1900-1930., 30 items. (Box-folder 10:8)
  - Miscellaneous contracts, 1900-1934., 28 items. (Box-folder 10:9)
  - Deeds, 1910-1920. (Box-folder 10:10-13)
    - Deeds: A-B, ca. 1910s and 1920s., 8 items. (Box-folder 10:10)
    - Deeds: C-L, 1910s-19s0s., 17 items. (Box-folder 10:11)
    - Deeds: M-P, 1910s-1920s., 11 items. (Box-folder 10:12)
    - Deeds: T-W, 1910s-1920s., 3 items. (Box-folder 10:13)
  - Insurance Policies, 1931-1932., 5 items. (Box-folder 10:14)
  - Receipts, 1895-1935, n.d. (Box-folder 10:15-23)
    - Receipts, 1895-1898., 20 items. (Box-folder 10:15)
    - Receipts, 1909-1917., 18 items. (Box-folder 10:16)
    - Receipts, 1918., 36 items. (Box-folder 10:17)
    - Receipts, 1922-1929., 25 items. (Box-folder 10:18)
    - Receipts, 1931., 15 items. (Box-folder 10:19)
    - Receipts, 1932., 40 items. (Box-folder 10:20)
    - Receipts, 1933-1935., 19 items. (Box-folder 10:21)
    - Receipts, n.d., 23 items. (Box-folder 10:22)
    - Unsigned, typewritten copies of receipts, 1910-1935., 22 items. (Box-folder 10:23)
  - Cancelled checks, 1914-1934. (Box-folder 10:24-25)
    - Cancelled checks, 1914-1918., 33 items. (Box-folder 10:24)
    - Cancelled checks, 1925-1934., 130 items. (Box-folder 10:25)
  - Miscellaneous Items, 1900-1935, n.d. (Box-folder 10:26-35)
    - Miscellaneous statements and inventories, 1900-1935., 54 items. (Box-folder 10:26)
    - Business cards, n.d., 6 items. (Box-folder 10:27)
    - Advertisements and schedules, 1911-1933., 6 items. (Box-folder 10:28)
    - Lists of names, n.d., 17 items. (Box-folder 10:29)
    - Miscellaneous hand-written papers, n.d., 26 items. (Box-folder 10:30)
    - Miscellaneous hand-written papers, n.d., 24 items. (Box-folder 10:31)
    - Miscellaneous hand-written papers, n.d., 8 items. (Box-folder 10:32)
    - Miscellaneous typed papers, n.d., 21 items. (Box-folder 10:33)
    - Miscellaneous papers belonging or pertaining to Herbert Barnes, 1920-1935., 30 items. (Box-folder 10:34)
    - Indexed notebook, n.d., 1 item. (Box-folder 10:35)
  Series 5: Books, Other Printed Material and Artifacts
- Books, Other Printed Material and Artifacts (Box 10-11)
  - Books and Other Printed Material, 1901-1924., Books 1-10 (Box 10)
    - Ledger books, ca. 1905., 2 items. Books 1 and 2 (Box 10)
    - Reports and Minutes of the 41st Convention of the Women's Christian Temperance Union of Virginia, 1923., 1 item. Book 3 (Box 10)
    - Anti-Saloon League Yearbook of 1914, 1914., 1 item. Book 4 (Box 10)
    - Anti-Prohibition Manual of 1917, 1917., 1 item. Book 5 (Box 10)
    - Democratic Campaign book, 1922, 1922., 1 item. Book 6 (Box 10)
    - Democratic Campaign Book, 1924, 1924., 1 item. Book 7 (Box 10)
    - By-laws of Wachapreague Council No. 96 Jr. A.U.O.M., 1901., 1 item. Book 8 (Box 10)
    - Budgets for the Commonwealth of Virginia, 1920-1924., 2 items. Book 9 and 10 (Box 11)
      Book 9 encompasses the years 1920-1922 and Book 10 encompasses the years 1922-1924.
  - Artifact, 1924., 1 item. Artifact 1. (Box 11)
    Davis-Bryan button from the 1924 presidential election.
  Series 6: Addition 1994.88
- Addition 1994.88, 1935-1941. (Folder 1-7)
  Letters from G. Walter Mapp (1873-1941) to his son John A. Mapp who was a student at the College of William and Mary, 1931-1935, and National Youth Administration Director for Eastern Virginia. Letters give fatherly advice, local and state news, and family news.
  Series 7: Addition 1995.50
- Addition 1995.50, 1891. (Othertype 1995.50)
  Catalogue of the College of William and Mary and State Male Normal College, session 1890-1891. Richmond, Va.: Whittet & Shepperson, Printers, Tenth and Main Streets, 1891. (Lists G. Walter Mapp as student.)